8theme.com 2019-02-26

# Privacy Policy

#### Privacy Policy

We respect your right to privacy. This policy summarises what personally identifiable information we may collect, and how we can use this information. This policy also describes other important topics concerning your privacy.

#### Information Collection

We will only collect personally identifiable information (such as name, title, company name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address) that you voluntarily provide through our website or e-mail. We will collect general information (such as the type of browser you use, the files you request, and the domain name and country from which you request information) to improve our web site and better satisfy your needs.

If you use a credit card to purchase products from our site, your name on the credit card, the credit card number, expiration date and billing address will be encrypted as it passes over the Internet. 8theme.com does not keep your credit card information for online credit-card transactions, but such information is simply passed through our contracted payment processing vendor.

#### Use of Information

Names and email addresses and other information which collected from customers at the time of a sale in order to complete the purchase. We do not share the information with third parties. We are firmly against spam and neither participate nor promote any activities that assist spammers.

#### Security

When we collect personal information directly from you, we follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. There is no 100% safe way of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage. So we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may at any time, without notice to you and in its sole discretion, amend this policy from time to time. Please review this policy periodically. Your continued use of our websites after any such amendments signifies your acceptance thereof.

We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.ok
